We made it, out of us.
That's what we do.
Oh, I missed her.
Excuse me.
Can I get your poster?
Yes, of course.
I'm proud of you.
Proud Columbia alum.
Good to meet you.
You too.
Hi, Susan.
I'm Amanda.
Thank you for being here.
Thank you.
It's putting yourselves and your body and your mind and your privilege in a position to help
platform others and to acknowledge that there are people who are benefiting and who are turning
a blind eye and you are making it impossible for them to do it.
And all of you guys here who are doing it, I hope you understand how important it is that
you are here because your bodies in this country matter more.
There's a whole Black Lives Matter movement because of that.
So you Jewish people who are here, just understand we appreciate you.
We see that you see the truth that needs to be seen.
And for somebody like myself, who is always trying to awake people and wake them up and
try to get them to understand.
It's just so incredible to see so many of you all who understand because you are going
to be here, but you're also going to be in other places.
You're going to be in other offices.
You're going to be in other buildings and you are going to carry this legacy of liberation.
I'm sure.
What's up, bro?
I'll send jail support.
I got you.
Thank you.
For what?
For nothing.
For chanting.
With a pot.
That's a difference.
She wasn't doing shit.
She was literally beating a pot.
Not being in the designated police zone.
Now she's arrested.
What designated police zone?
What is the designated police zone?
There's not enough room on sidewalk.
On one sidewalk.
Yeah.
This is not a public sidewalk.
What?
All y'all doing is babysitting.
Y'all standing here and getting paid.
For what?
You don't even make sense.
I hope it's worth it.
All of y'all.
All y'all.
I hope it's worth it.
I hope it's worth it. I hope it's worth it. I hope it's worth it, all of y'all. I hope it's worth it.